<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ThirtyDays</string>
    <string name="item_1">Zone out for a while</string>
    <string name="desc_1">Need permission to just turn your brain off with a movie or series? Here it is. "Taking your attention and putting it on something else, versus thinking about all the things that are going on in your life is a nice pause," No, you don\'t want to get sucked into episode after episode (being sedentary as a way of life is the opposite of self-care) but getting caught up in a narrative can give the busy brain a break. "Those things will still be there, but you'll have a reboot, so when you go back to them, you'll have a different perspective."</string>
    <string name="item_2">Dial up some love</string>
    <string name="desc_2">Need permission to just turn your brain off with a movie or series? Here it is. "Taking your attention and putting it on something else, versus thinking about all the things that are going on in your life is a nice pause," No, you don\'t want to get sucked into episode after episode (being sedentary as a way of life is the opposite of self-care) but getting caught up in a narrative can give the busy brain a break. "Those things will still be there, but you'll have a reboot, so when you go back to them, you'll have a different perspective."</string>
    <string name="item_3">Be inspired by #SelfcareSunday</string>
    <string name="desc_3">No matter where you turn, someone is probably talking about self-care — the movement that’s all about putting you first physically, mentally, and emotionally. And before you think, I have zero time for myself, repeat this: self-care is not selfish. Because when you put your best foot forward, everybody wins. Over the next few months, spend some time making every single week count (and realizing how valuable this is for your health).</string>
    <string name="item_4">Spend 20 minutes clearing clutter.</string>
    <string name="desc_4">Getting rid of that stack of mail, the pile of shoes by the door, and the overflow from your closet may improve your sense of well-being. Studies have linked cluttered environments with stress and lower self-control (say, around food), which can put a damper on your physical health.Try snapping a photo of a messy area of your home, then devote 20 minutes to picking up. When the timer rings, pause for at least 10 minutes (or the rest of the day if you like!). Replacing open-ended cleaning sessions with a timed window makes the chore less overwhelming, says Rachel Hoffman, author of Cleaning Sucks. And comparing the “before” and “after” photos will give you a sense of accomplishment.</string>
    <string name="item_5">Lift weights while you watch TV</string>
    <string name="desc_5">The risk of cardiac events like heart attack and stroke was up to 70% lower for people who lifted weights twice a week than for those who never did, a study from Iowa State found. Weight training also improves bone density and balance. Buy a set of light dumbbells (3 to 8 lbs), and while you watch TV, do moves like bicep curls and lunges.If you don’t have weights in your home, drop into a plank and hold it. Start by setting yourself up as if you’re going to do a push-up: Plant your shoulders over your hands, engage your core and your glutes as you keep your body in a straight line and hold for as long as you can. A pound of muscle burns four times as many calories as a pound of fat does, so the more muscle you have, the more calories you’ll torch.</string>
    <string name="item_6">Switch from late nights to long brunches.</string>
    <string name="desc_6">One study found that 41% of parents said too many late activities — their own and their kids’ — kept them from getting a good night’s sleep. Sleep is key to feeling in control and making a good decision (as well as a bunch of other health benefits.) Aim for seven to eight hours, and keep the thermostat at 67°F for the best dozing environment. Remember, “No, thanks, let’s do brunch!” may be the healthiest solution to too many afternoon and evening get-togethers (even if they are digital in nature!).</string>
</resources>